Guide to the Community, Food & Agriculture Program records, 1960-2000.
Community, Food & Agriculture Program records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Community, Food & Agriculture Program records, 1960-2000.
21-46-3763
Cornell University.Community, Food & Agriculture Program
27 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Publications, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, publications, reports and memos about the program.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Community, Food & Agriculture Program (CFAP) was launched as the Cornell Farming Alterntatives Program in 1986, which focused on research, training and outreach materials designed to help struggling dairy farmers transition to more diverse and profitable agricultural enterprises. In 2002 the program changed its name to CFAP and remained committed to the mission of sustaining farms and communities in New York State and the Northeast. The program ended in 2006.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, publications, reports and memos about the program.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Community, Food & Agriculture Program.; Cornell Farming Alternatives Program.
Subjects:
Farmers--Socioeconomic status.; Dairying.; Agriculture--New York (State); Sustainable agriculture--New York (State).; Agriculture--United States.; Rural development.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Closed for processing
CONTAINER LIST
- Proposals- Part I, 1993-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Proposals- Part II, 1993-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Northeast Training and Support Network for Agriculture Development- Profile and 2000 Annual Report, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Northeast Training and Support Network for Agriculture Development- 1998-1999 Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Northeast Training and Support Network for Agriculture Development- Proposal 1998, Budget 2000, 1998, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Northeast Sustainable Agriculture Working Group and Cornell University, Contract, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scientific Cooperation Program, University of Vermont, "Northeast Dairy Farmers", 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fund for Rural America, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education Program 1994, Mid-Atlantic Consortium 1996, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Association for Sustainable Agriculture 1998, Regional Identity Marketing of Agriculture and Food 2001, 1998, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fund for Rural America- Small Scale Food Processing for Rural Development, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Managing Change in Agriculture 1997, Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development 1998, 1997, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Conferences, 1992, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Transitions Conferences Part I, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Transitions Conferences Part II, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Public Relations, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agriculture Task Force Report, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Testimonials and Letters of Support, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Special Lists, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Farming Alternatives Program (FAP) Project Ideas, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Seaway Trails-Regional Agri-Tourism Marketing Diversification, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Proposals- City Farm 1997; Hatch 1998-2001; Web-based Training for Evaluating the Feasibility of New Farm-based Enterprises 1997, 1997, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Proposal Preparation and Federal-State Marketing Improvement Program Submission, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- The Business Incubation Function of Farmers Markets in Rural Enterprise Development, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Fund for Rural America- Center Planning, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Proposals-Ginseng 1997; Agriculture Economic Development 1994; Cultural, Small-scale, Sustainable Food Production Project for Youth 1997, 1997, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Farming Alternatives Program (FAP) Quarterly and Annual Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- FAP Press Release and Articles, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Small-scale Growers Co-ops Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- FAP Budget Proposals- The City Farms 1997, Ethnic Markets and Sustainable Agriculture, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Proposals- Community Food Retail Farmers’ Markets and Rural Development, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Small-scale Food Processing Workshop, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fund for Rural America, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Proposals- Hatch 1998-2001, Center for Food Entrepreneurship 2000, Small Farms 2000, Marketing and Management of Sheep and Goats 1999-2000, 1998-2001, 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Farmer-Centered, Value-added, Processing and Marketing Opportunities, Research and Development Project 1997, Hatch Proposal 1998, 1997, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Small-scale Food Processing in New York, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Retail Farmers’ Markets and Rural Development Funding Application, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- MAC- Using GIS Planning Grant Proposal, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Managing Change in Agriculture, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Sustainable Agriculture in Northeast Communities Funding, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Commercial Small-scale Food Processing in New York, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Job Announcements, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Conferences 1998, Rural Update Newsletter 1996, 1998, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, Contacts, Orders, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Judy Green Memos and Originals, Sustainable Agriculture Coordinator Position, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Statewide Strategic Planning Process for Sustainable Food and Agriculture Systems, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Related Newspaper Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education Program Progress Report, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education- Budgets 1995-1996; Reports, Publicity, Administrative 1995-1997, 1995-1996, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education Proposals, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education: Correspondence, Surveys, Notes, Updates, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Farming for the Future Workshop, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Farming for the Future Workshop, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Farming for the Future Study Tours, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- New York State Agency Programs: 4-H Foundation 1990-1991; Rural Development 1987, 1990-1991, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Funding: Church Groups 1996; Agora 1986-1992; American Farmland 1992; Great Lakes Presentation 1995, Veatch, 1996, 1986-1992, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Surdna Foundation 1993-1994; Kellog Foundation 1996-1997; Wallace Genetic Foundation 1993, 1993-1994, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Wallace Institute for Alternative Agriculture, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Foundations (Box 3, Folder 10)
- The Role of Small-scale Growers Coop Sustainable Northeast Agriculture, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Sustainable Agriculture Through Sustainable Community Development, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Funding Sources, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Apple Earth Grants II 1993; The Aspen Institute 1992, 1993, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Federal Agencies- AARC; USDA; FMHA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- USDA Paperwork, Forms, Information Sheets, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Deer Farming- Symposium, Files, Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- “The Compleat Deer Farmer”, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bradford City Presentation; Farmer to Farmer, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Worksheet Masters for Farming Alternatives (Box 3, Folder 20)
- NCAT- Overhead Originals, Materials, Notes (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Development Group Profile, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Development Groups Retreats, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Survey Results, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Transitions II, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Opportunities Seminar and Trade Show, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Meetings- Notes, Agendas Correspondences, Presentations, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Transitions Conference 1993; Farming Alternatives Program (FAP) Reports 1993-1994, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Transitions Conference 1993-1994, 1993, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Farming for the Future, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- New York Farming Alternatives Conference, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Northeast Organic and Sustainable Farms Network, Farming Alternatives, and Extension Review Summaries and Reports, 1987, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Transitions- Logistics, Agendas, etc., 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Farming Alternatives Program- Selected Sustainable Agriculture Resources (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Farming for the Future, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- General Marketing Planning and Overviews, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Marketing Innovations, Resources, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Market Research, Competition Analysis, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Consumer Trends and Demographics, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Marketing Animal Products, Fruit/Veg Specialty, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Direct Marketing- General Information, 1986-1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Direct Marketing Resources, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Promotion/Advertising, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Agritourism Resources, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Cooperatives #1, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cooperatives #2, 1983-2000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cooperatives #3, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Diversification Resources, 1986-1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Diversification Theory, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Diversification Tools (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Alternative Enterprises (Box 5, Folder 4)
- E-Commerce (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Exports (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Farmers Markets (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Farmers Markets Publications (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Roadside Stands (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Value Added (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Value Adding- Examples (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Beer (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Wines (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Food Processing (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Food Labels (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Mobile Processing Units (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Resources- Small Bus (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Shared Use Kitchens (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Vending Suppliers (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Food Safety (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Food Systems (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Food Systems (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Community Food Security (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Globalization/ Industrialization Concentration (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Food Travels (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Eating Locally (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Local Foods Nutrition (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Rural-Urban Linkages (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Rural-Urban Examples (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Community Agricultural Development (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Community Agricultural Development (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Local/Regional Issues and Programs (Box 6, Folder 11)
- General Process and Planning (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Planning Guides and Workbooks (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Rural Agricultural Development (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Rural Sociology Issues (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Civic Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 16)
- New York State Economic Outlook and Statistics (Box 7, Folder 1)
- New York State Statistics, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New York State Studies (Box 7, Folder 3)
- New York State Studies (Box 7, Folder 4)
- USDA Stats- 1997 Census of Agriculture, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Policy (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Emerging Policy Issues (Box 7, Folder 7)
- New York State Policy (Box 7, Folder 8)
- New York State Policy- General (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Ag and Markets Leg Proposal on Agriculture Diversification, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- New York State Economic Development Plan (Box 7, Folder 11)
- USA Policy- General (Box 7, Folder 12)
- 1990 Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- 1995 Farm Bill, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NYSAWG Farm Bill Dialogue, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- 2002 Farm Bill, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Policy Resources (Box 7, Folder 17)
- New York State Agriculture Policy Organizations (Box 7, Folder 18)
- US Agriculture Policy Organizations (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Policy and Ag/Rural Development (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Environmental Regulations (Box 7, Folder 21)
- High-Yield Agriculture (Policy Issues) (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Policy and Marketing- State and Federal Initiatives (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Policy and Sustainable Ag (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Policy and Land grants (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Policy and Land Use (Box 7, Folder 26)
- General Policy and Land Use (Box 7, Folder 27)
- General Policy and Land Use (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Ag Districts (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Conservation Easements (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Farm Land Stats (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Farm Land Preservation (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Farm Land Preservation (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Land Trusts (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Ryoko Tsukamoto (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Literature: Farmers’ Market Project (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Farmers’ Markets and Rural Economic Development-FAP, Farmers’ Market Project (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Examples of Farmers' Markets, Economic Development (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Related Projects: Farmers’ Market Project (Box 8, Folder 6)
- NETSN Farmers’ Market Study (Judy) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Wisconsin Study (Box 8, Folder 8)
- USDA Ag Marketing Services (Study with Monika 120th and Nelson Bills) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Update, May-92 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 1992 Annual Report, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Winter 1993, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Spring 1993, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Summer 1993, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Fall 1993, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Annual Report, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Winter 1993-1994, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Spring 1994, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Summer 1994, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Fall 1994, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Annual Report, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Annual Report, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Winter 1994/1995, 1994/1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Spring 1995, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Summer 1995, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Fall 1995, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Newsletter Material, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Annual Report, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Annual Report, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Annual Report, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Winter 1996, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Spring 1996, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Spring 1996 Newsletter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Summer 1996, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Summer 1996 Newsletter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Summer 1996 Newsletter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Fall 1996, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Things for Annual Report, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Annual Report, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Winter 1997, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Spring/Summer 1997, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Fall 1997, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Fall 1997 Newsletter, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Newsletter Winter, 1997/1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Winter 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Spring 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Spring NL, May, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Summer 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Summer 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Farming Alternatives Program (FAP) Newsletter- Summer ‘98, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Fall 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Newsletter Fall 1998, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Winter 1999, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Newsletter Winter ‘99, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Spring 1999, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Newsletter Spring ‘99, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Summer 1999, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Fall 1999, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Winter 2000, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Spring 2000, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Summer 2000, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Fall 2000, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Winter 2001, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Spring 2001, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Summer 2001, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Fall 2001, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Winter 2002, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Spring 2002, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Summer 2002, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Fall 2002, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Folder not labeled- contents: Summer 2003, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Winter 2004, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Spring 2004, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Folder unlabeled- contents: Summer 2004, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Agritourism Resources (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Agritourism Resources (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Spencer-Venetteh Project (Box 9, Folder 3)
- White Post Modern Farm Centre (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Agritourism Workshop (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Agritourism Study DE Log, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Agritourism Study, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Agritourism: Carol Doolittle, cases 1-15 & 149-160 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Agritourism: Norman Greig, cases 16-103 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Julie’s Evaluations (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Agritourism: Gail Black, cases 161-198 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Agritourism: Long Acres Farm, cases 214-267 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Agritourism: Side Hill Acres, cases 268-298 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Co-op Farm Store Concept Paper(s) (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Co-op Farm Store FHA Financing (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Co-op Farm Store Grange Store Concept (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Co-op Farm Store Social Responsibility (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Co-op Farm Store Name (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Co-op Farm Store Contacts (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Co-op Farm Store Books/Publications (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Co-op Farm Store Models/Competition (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Co-op Farm Store Specialty Food Market (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Co-op Farm Store Loans (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Co-op Farm Store SVBC (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Co-op Farm Store Technical Assistance (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Co-op Farm Store Franchising (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Co-op Farm Store Retail Management (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Co-op Farm Store Idea Scraps (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Co-op Farm Store Models (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Co-op Farm Store Cooperatives (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Co-op Farm Store ARC (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Co-op Farm Store ARC Entrepr. Initiative (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Co-op Farm Store Incorporation (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Retail Farmers Market Study (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Retail Farmers Market Study FM Study (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Retail Farmers Market Study: NETSN FM Study notes (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Retail Farmers Market Study case study materials (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Retail Farmers Market Study Background Data (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Farmers Market Resource (Box 10, Folder 1)
- FM Presentation (Box 10, Folder 2)
- FM Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Non-Economic Impact Study (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Not labeled (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Sheep and Goat/ Halal Meeting (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Sheep and Goat/ Halal Marketing (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Venison Marketing (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Not labeled (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Place-based Resources (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Market Orders (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Regional Identity (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Grapebelt Study (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Lake Erie Grapebelt (Box 10, Folder 14)
- New York State Viticulture (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Heritage Agriculture (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Essence of Place (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Agritourism Presentations (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Agroforestry (Box 10, Folder 19)
- CFAP (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Business Planning- FAP Guide (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Business Planning- Transitions Conference (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Growing Home (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Home Business (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hops (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Planning Meeting, 3/23/2006 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Coop Study (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Lists - Co-op (Various) (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Co-op Letters/Postcards/Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Co-op Meeting, 23-Mar (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Co-op Notes (Telemeetings, etc.) (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Co-op Study Proposals (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Co-op Study Proposals (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Co-op Study Director Lists (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Co-op Directors Survey Original (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Co-op Directors Surveys (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Co-op Directors’ Survey (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Not Included Directors (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Co-op Manager’s Survey (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Co-op Manager’s Survey Response (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Co-op Member’s Survey (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Co-op Member Survey Original (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Northeast Cooperative Member Addresses (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Co-op Member Survey Response (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Co-op Member Surveys (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Member Surveys Received (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Member Surveys #2 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Co-op Presentations (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Co-op Study Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Co-op Study Stats (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Co-op Survey Various (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Innovative Farming Idea List (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Ag Econ Development (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Developing New Mark (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Engaging the Public (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Urban Connections (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Who Will Farm? (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Community Ag Dev (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Basic Formula to Create CSA (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Alternative Agriculture Opp Taxonomy (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Agritourism in New York: Management & Operations (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Adding Value for Sustainability (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Compleat Deer Farmer (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Compleat Deer Farmer (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Sea Grant Considerations (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Cultivating Farm, Neighbor, & Community Relations (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Diversified Rural Livelihood Strategies (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Experience in New York State (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Farmers’ Markets (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Farmers’ Markets (Box 12, Folder 21)
- For-Free Pond Fishing (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Growing Home (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Horticultural Innovators (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Ithaca Farmers’ Market, Kate Alexander (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Farming Alternatives (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Land, People, and Profits (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Land, People, and Profits, Corer & Section I (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Land, People, and Profits, Public Education Team (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Land, People, and Profits, Smart Growth Team (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Land, People, and Profits, Farmers’ Markets Team (Box 12, Folder 31)
- List for Nat Org/Ecol Landscape Network (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Practical, Profitable, & Sustainable (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Small Scale Grower Co-ops (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Steps in the Management Process (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Jason Frost (Two Mills) (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Farming Alternatives Survey 1987 (FAS) #00002-00101, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- FAS 1987 #00104-00147, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- FAS 1987 #00148-00195, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- FAS 1987 #00196-00252, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- FAS 1987 #00252-00284, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- FAS 1987 #00286-00352, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- FAS 1987 #00353-00391, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- FAS 1987 #00395-00532, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- FAS 1987 #00539-00598, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- FAS 1987 #00601-00705, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- FAS 1987 #00706 - #00803, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Survey - Minot, July, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Questionnaires Geo Desp (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Printing Order Form, Letterhead, Envelopes (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Alternative Farming Stats (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Empty Folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
- LOTUS (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Other Critical Problems (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Project Estimates (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Survey Analysis (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Letters (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Farmer Surveys (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Center For Local Food (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Brochures (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Rural Futures Newsletters (Box 13, Folder 20)
- NTS Agriculture & Markets Press Releases (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Originals, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Originals, Jan-Jun,1994 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Publication Referral Letter (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Resource Sheets (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Sustainable Agriculture - Virgin Copy (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Adding Value for Sustainability (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Adding Value: Fostering Locally-Owned Food Processing Businesses (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Adding Value With Small-Scale Dairy (Box 13, Folder 29)
- AG Economic Development (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Agritourism (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Alternative Enterprises For Urban Farmers (Box 13, Folder 32)
- CAD: A Collabi Process New (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Community AG Development (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Complete Deer Farmer - Originals of Most Material (Box 13, Folder 35)